The biggest problem here
is not the economy, it's not GLP-1s,
it's not the
algorithm, it's you. And I'm sorry,
but I think you may think
you are more special than everyone else,
and you may think that you don't have to
go through every other fucking hurdle
that everyone else did.
And I'm here to remind you that you do.
Now,
I know not all of you understand Brazilian
jiu-jitsu, but just listen to what
I'm about to say. At 27,
I went full time at going online, and
the same year,
I did my first ever Brazilian jiu-jitsu
session.
Some of you might think I'm very good at
jiu-jitsu because the footage that you're
watching now is nine years in the making.
I've been training jiu-jitsu for as long
as I have been fully online.
For my first two years,
I had the shit kicked out of me.
I began at a gym where my path to
improving was to suffer.
I quit that gym because my coach
was legitimately a psychopath.
But I kept turning up,
I kept improving with tiny margins,
and I kept coming
back.
You don't see the nights where I'd walk
out the gym, sit on the floor,
too tired to even stand on my skateboard
and skateboard home.
I'd sit there defeated, sore, and I
was literally shaking from
overexertion.
I would have the shit kicked out of me by
all the higher belts.
But then as time went on,
I got my blue belt,
then I got my purple belt.
Now I've got my brown belt. Now,
nearly 10 years on, I can beat
95% of people in the entire sport.
But not because I'm special, not because
I'm athletic, not because I'm talented,
but because of all the years that I
ate shit.
I know for a fact you've never seen a
video of me from 2014,
2015, 2016, or even 2017.
The same reason you've not
seen footage of me rolling as a white
belt, a blue belt, or a purple belt.
And I hope by now you're starting to see
the fucking parallels